Guide to the Edward W. Sites Papers, 1958-2019 UA.90.F109
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1991-2002 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Student Records Codebook (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Stenson, Kiernan (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Strategic Planning, 2000-2007 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Student Directories, School of Social Work, 1964-1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Student Handbook, School of Social Work, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Volume 19)
- Student Organization Newsletters, 1987-2012 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Syllabi (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
- Travis, Georgia (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Undergraduate Social Work Education (Box 27, Folder 5)
- University of District of Columbia, IV-E (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
- University of Pittsburgh Employment, Edward W. Sites (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Urban Analysis, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Urban Organizing (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Vocational Rehabilitation Administration, United States, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Woodland Hills Desegregation Case, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Workload Study, Children Youth and Families, Allegheny County, Pennsylvania (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Youth Development Center, See Loysville Youth Development Center, Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Bernstein, Sol [DVD], October 26, 1984 (Box 28, Item 1)
- Child Welfare: An Inside View of Social Work in Action, Mary H. Page, Judith A. Martin, Edward W. Sites, and Richard A. Wells [3/4 Inch Videocassette], 1980 (Box 28, Item 2)
- Child Welfare: An Inside View of Social Work in Action, Mary H. Page, Judith A. Martin, Edward W. Sites, and Richard A. Wells [DVD], 1980 (Box 28, Item 3)
- Child Welfare: An Inside View of Social Work in Action. Instructor's Manual, Mary H. Page, Judith A. Martin, Edward W. Sites, and Richard A. Wells, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Council for the Advancement of Social Groupwork Practice [DVD set], November 29, 1979 (Box 28, Item 5-7)
- Dellums, Ronald V. State of the Nation. Keynote Address, 1971 National Association of Social Workers Delegate Assembly [Audio Cassette] (Box 28, Item 8)
- Dybwad, Gunnar, Mainstream Approach to Services for the Retarded Lecture, School of Social Work, University of Pittsburgh School of Social Work [Audio Cassettes], November 14, 1969 (Box 28, Item 9-10)
- Engaging Families in the Helping Process: Basic Techniques, Richard A. Wells and Mary H. Page [3/4 inch Videocassette], 1979 (Box 28, Item 11)
- Engaging Families in the Helping Process: Basic Techniques, Richard A. Wells and Mary H. Page [DVD], 1979 (Box 28, Item 12)
- Engaging Families in the Helping Process: Basic Techniques. Instructor's Manual, Richard A. Wells and Mary H. Page [3/4 inch Videocassette], 1979 (Box 28, Item 13)
- Ginsberg, Mitchell I. Mainstreaming the Quality of Social Work Education Lecture, Annual Program Meeting, Council on Social Work Education [Audio Cassette], March 11, 1981 (Box 28, Item 14)
- Interview of Ruth Middleman by Ruth Middleman and Paula Dronie [VHS], October 25, 1986 (Box 28, Item 15)
- Interview of Mary Lou Sommers by Ruth Middleman [VHS], October 25, 1986 (Box 28, Item 16)
- Interview of Gertrude Wilson by Ruth Middleman [VHS], November 11, 1982 (Box 28, Item 17)
- Kahn, Alfred J. Perspectives on National Family Policy Lecture, School of Social Work [Audio Cassette], April 4, 1978 (Box 28, Item 18-19)
- Knopka, Gisela [DVD], October 25, 1986 (Box 28, Item 20)
- Lehrman, Louis J. [Audio Cassettes] (Box 28, Folder 21-22)
- Lehrman, Louis J. [CD] (Box 28, Item 23)
- Piven, Frances Fox Lecture, School of Social Work, University of Pittsburgh [Audio Cassette], January 31, 1974 (Box 28, Item 24)
- Redl, Fritz Lecture, School of Social Work, University of Pittsburgh Lecture [Audio Cassette], May 9, 1974 (Box 28, Item 25)
- Sommers, Mary Lou [DVD], October 25, 1986 (Box 28, Item 26)
- Special Needs Adoptions: Resources for Success, Copyright Edward W. Sites [3/4 Inch Videocassette], 1981 (Box 28, Item 27)
- Special Needs Adoptions: Resources for Success, Copyright Edward W. Sites [VHS], 1981 (Box 28, Item 28)
- Special Needs Adoptions: Resources for Success, Copyright Edward W. Sites [DVD], 1981 (Box 28, Item 29)
- Special Needs Adoptions: Resources for Success, Discussion Guide, 1981 (Box 28, Item 30)
- Wilson, Gertrude [DVD], November 11,1980 (Box 28, Item 31)
- Field Education Manual, School of Social Work, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Item 1)
- Newsletters, Associate Dean Michael A. Patchner, October 1992-October 1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Staff Members, School of Social Work, 1966-2018 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Student Directories, School of Social Work, 1962-1974, 1987-1988, 1993-2005 (Box 30, Item 2-37)
- Student Handbooks, School of Social Work, 1977-1991 (Box 30, Item 38-50)
- Student Handbooks, School of Social Work, 1991-2003 (Box 31, Item 1-12)
- Committee Assignments, School of Social Work, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Child Welfare Training Program, Space, Mechanicsburg, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- CWEB/CWEL/CWTP Anniversaries, 2022 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Admissions and Graduates, 1995-2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Predecessor, 1989-1994 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Distinguished Alumni Committee, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Hathway, Marion, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Katz, Rosalyn B., n.d. (Box 31, Folder 8)
- National Association of Social Workers - Pennsylvania Social Worker Complaint, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Sites, Edward W., Advisees, 1966-2006 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Sites, Edward W., Presentations, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Smalley, Ruth Elizabeth, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Teller, Sidney, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 13)